Marcelo Fioresi Guermandi

Milano, Italia



marcelofguermandi@gmail.com



351 742 9828



linkedin.com/in/marcelo-fioresi-guermandi



https://mrnfg.github.io

Summary

Professionista con più di 5 anni di esperienza con la Customer Experience (CX). Interessato e motivato a lavorare come Front-end Developer o UX/UI Designer. Esperto in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SQL, Photoshop e altre tecnologie. Sto studiando per diventare Full Stack Designer e Developer.

Experience



Claims Handler (Hybrid)

Generali Italia

Dec 2021 - Dec 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Fulfillment Associate

Amazon

Nov 2020 - Jul 2021 (9 months)

Tour Operator & Help Desk (Hybrid)

EZLINK - Hotels

Dec 2016 - Mar 2020 (3 years 4 months)

Education



Centro Universitário Internacional UNINTER

Laurea Triennale, Analisi e Sviluppo di Sistemi Informatici 2017 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications



Photoshop for UX Design - LinkedIn



Cert Prep: Adobe Certified Associate - InDesign - LinkedIn



Become a User Experience Designer - LinkedIn

Skills

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML5 • JavaScript • Figma (Software) • Technical Support • Problem Solving • Technical Support • Self-Directed Learning • WordPress • Adobe Design Programs